authoritylabs.com 2014-06-29

# AuthorityLabs Privacy Policy - AuthorityLabs

We collect certain information relative to users who visit the site. AuthorityLabs does not make any attempt to obtain information that personally identifies our users who visit our site. It is not our policy to sell or otherwise provide access to such information to unaffiliated third parties. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission.

### Information Gathering and Usage

Any information that we collect is collected as part of our business practices in order to identify demographic information relative to users who access our site, assessing the number and type of user accessing various sections of our site, helping us determine what content and business concepts are working for us and/or are of interest to our visitors, determining technical design features and specifications and helping us assess systems performance. We also use such information in statistical form to assist us in business and marketing strategies and programs. We utilize software programs to create summary statistics which we utilize for the above purposes.

### Data Ownership

AuthorityLabs uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run AuthorityLabs. All search engine data collected through AuthorityLabs is owned by AuthorityLabs and licensed to its customers on an as-needed basis.

### Disclosure

Personal information AuthorityLabs collects is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

AuthorityLabs may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

We transfer information about you if AuthorityLabs is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, AuthorityLabs will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Changes to this policy

Although changes to our Privacy Policy are unlikley to be significant, AuthorityLabs may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your AuthorityLabs primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
